Dennis Kimathi

Full Stack and blockchain Engineer with a passion for building products that not only address user problems but also align seamlessly with business needs.

⊕ Nairobi, Kenya, KEN

<u>kimathidennis38@gmail.com</u> +254 743312265



About

I am a highly-motivated, creative and pro-active designer and web developer able to research, design and develop user experiences for various digital products including mobile applications, websites and web applications. I use my broad range of skills to execute designs that are clean, simple and effective.

Work Experience

Silvi Remote August 2023 - Present

Senior Frontend Developer

Focusing on developing user interfaces and enhancing user experiences. Collaborating with cross-functional teams to deliver efficient and responsive web applications. Utilizing technologies such as NextJS(React), TypeScript, and ensuring optimal integration with backend systems.

Chizaalabs Remote Apr 2017 - July 2022

UI/UX Consultant → Full Stack Developer

Designed and built web apps for clients across the globe. Built a (decentralized finance)defi social trading app for Loibon from scratch. Technologies: NextJS, React, TypeScript, GraphQL, Solidity, Firebase, The Graph,

Ryden International

Jan 2020 - Apr 2022

Digital Marketer

Successfully executed and optimized digital marketing campaigns. Crafted and implemented strategies that led to a 30% increase in brand visibility and a 25% growth in user engagement. Utilized a mix of SEO, SEM, and social media marketing to achieve targeted goals. Implemented data-driven approaches, resulting in a 20% improvement in campaign performance.

Education

Moringa School April 2022 - Nov 2022

Software Engineering

Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology

2015 - 2019

Bachelor's Degree in Real Estate

Skills

localhost:3000

1/2/24, 10:56 PM Dennis Kimathi | Full Stack and blockchain Engineer with a passion for building products that not only addre...

JavaScript TypeScript React/Next.js/Remix Node.js GraphQL Go Solidity
Firebase/Supabase/AppWrite Tailwind CSS React Testing Library Cypress Git
Docker Linux AWS GCP Heroku Vercel DigitalOcean MongoDB
PostgreSQL Redis The Graph IPFS OpenZeppelin Uniswap Chainlink

localhost:3000 2/3

Projects

Nafter

A marketplace platform for users to buy and sell Non-Fungible-Tokens

Side Project TypeScript

Next.js React Solidity

Celo

TumainiDAO

TumainiDAO is a nonprofit Decentralised Application Organization that looks to empower the African Girl Child

Hackathon JavaScript

React Solidity EthersJS

denniskimathi.dev

My personal website and blog. Built with Next.js and MDX

Side Project Next.js MDX

juakalike

a marketplace dapp built on celo blockchain

Side Project Next.js

Solidity celo wagmi hooks

CarbonHero

a marketplace dapp built on celo blockchain

Hackathon Next.js

ToucanSDK Celo Graphql

Graph Protocol

CeloDev Stream

Token streaming dapp built with superfluid that rewards developers in celo ecosystem

Hackathon Next.js

SuperfluidSDK Celo

Hardhat Solidity

LumenPay

A Crypto Payroll Platform to help employers to manage their payroll and pay their employees with crypto

React TailwindCSS NodeJS

Express

Web3Guardian

A telegram bot that leverages the UTU Web3 Protocol to provide reputation checks on telegram users

Typescript Web3

Telegram Bot NodeJS

Ethers.js UTU Protocol

localhost:3000 3/3